I am not a thief.
How dare you run?!
Are you hiding more jewels
in that bag, huh?!
Here! Check it!
You're so mean.
You're so cruel to me.
Because I'm just a maid?
I didn't steal anything!
You can even check
my fingerprints!
Ma'am, they probably stole it!
They've been on my back
since forever!
What?!
Are you seriously
blaming us, huh?!
Why would we go through
all this trouble?
We don't know you.
You're just some pathetic,
toilet-scrubbing nobody
playing dress up!
[BRENDA LAUGHING]
And that dress needs
a few more cuts.
[KATY] Ma'am! Ma'am Brenda!
Guards!
[KATY] Ma'am, no. No!
- Ma'am! No!
- No! Ma'am, no!
No, ma'am! [CRIES]
- [BRENDA LAUGHING]
- [KATY] Hannah.
Hannah!
[BRENDA] (In Korean) You bitch!
- Ma'am, enough!
- (In Korean) You witch!
- [BRENDA SCREAMING]
- Ma'am!
- Ma'am, please stop!
- (In Korean) Ah! You witch!
- Ma'am, stop!
- [BRENDA LAUGHING]
- Stop. Enough.
- You are a thief!
[WHIMPERS]
[SCREAMS]
Brenda, stop it!
- [HANNAH CRYING]
- Stop it!
Please stop. [CRIES]
Enough. Please stop.
- [EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SOBBING]
Whatever was lost or stolen,
I will pay for all of it.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Uh... Sorry,
filming isn't allowed here.
Guards! Katy, get back to work.
Um, I hope you can just...
- ...keep it to yourselves.
- Shh.
(In Korean) Why are you
protecting this trash, Daniel?!
Who is she?!
I'm sorry, Madam.
I can't tell you.
Come back here!
I'm your boss' wife!
You answer to me!
It's okay.
You're safe now.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
[HUFFING]